I must say, I'm impressed you found me.
Finding one of your other selves
in the city isn't so hard for me anymore.
My, my. You sure weren't gentle.
I didn't kill her. I held back.
And what brings you here?
I take it you haven't come for a tea party?
I want you to ask you a question.
A question, is it?
Whether I can answer or not
depends on the question.
Zaphkiel is an Angel
that manipulates time.
And each and every 12 of the dials
has some sort of different power.
Of those 12, does one have a bullet
to send someone you shoot into the past?
Supposing there is one,
what would you say?
That I want to borrow your power.
You suggesting that I use
Yod Bet for your sake?
Is that what you're saying?
Yes.
Well, here's my answer.
Unfortunately, I'm afraid
I'll have to disappoint you.
You may have incredible power,
but it means nothing if you can't hit me.
I'm so being underestimated.
Just out of curiosity, what would
you be doing with Yod Bet?
I... want you to send me
to August 3rd, five years ago.
Five years ago, you say?
To go back five years and make my
dad and mom's deaths never happen!
With this power, I'll change history!
Is that so?
And what will you do if I refuse?
Make you agree by any means necessary.
Hmm? You've gone and said it now...
But, whatever.
I was worried about using Yod Bet
without testing it first anyway.
So I'll have you be my guinea pig.
Really?
Now, come to me!
Zaphkiel!
Zaphkiel...
Yod Bet.
Go and show me.
How mad and foolish trying
to change the world is...
...and how far God permits it.
"Tengu City Municipal Hospital"
Ugh, Shido... I'm hungry.
"Episode Eight:
'Demon King of Descending Darkness"
Shido, you're not giving our kinswoman
the forbidden fruit before us, are you?
Complaint. Shido is forgetting that
he's our property first and foremost.
Hey! Me, too, me, too!
Yeah, yeah. I'll grab you
something, so hang tight.
Do you two want anything?
"Kotori"
Yoshino's phone?
U-Um, Shido?
No, Yoshino. This isn't...
What's all this ruckus about?
Gah!
No, Natsumi! This isn't...!
You rotten fiend!
Sh-Shido!
Y-You did perverted things to Yoshino
while I was sleeping right beside her?!
It's a misunderstanding!
I was just reaching... for this!
"Kotori"
Kotori?!
Hello? Yoshino?
Kotori?! Is that you?!
This is... five years ago...
Metatron, Mal'akh!
Five years ago in Tengu City's Nankou area...
Dad... Mom...!
Shido...
I found... you.
I found you...
I found you! I found you!
I finally found you!
Metatron!
Hmm? Attacking me out of nowhere...
I was wondering who it might be.
You're a Spirit?
And that Angel... Metatron?
What's the meaning of this?
I still have the Sephirah, so...
Hey, who are you?
Where did you come from?
Why did you attack me?
I see... You reversed the flow of time
using Zaphkiel, have you?
That's surprising... For her
to lend someone her powers...
Kadour!
You won't get away!
It seems the future me has earned
quite the grudge from you.
Sorry, but I can't let myself
be killed here by you.
I too have a wish I must make true.
A wish? For real?
You kill my dad and mom
and dare to have a wish?!
Screw you! Screw you! Screw you!
I won't give you time for your wish!
I won't give you time to pray!
Die without doing anything!
Disappear, leaving nothing behind!
Have nothing but regret
in your empty heart...
...and begone from the world!
Your dad and your mom?
Sorry, but maybe you have
the wrong person?
That was magnificent.
To think you could wield Metatron so well...
The birth of a powerful Spirit
should be celebrated.
You're...
That attack of yours
I'm delighted to witness.
This is all so my wish comes to pass.
Goodbye. It's about time I went on my way...
You're going nowhere!
...since I achieved my goal for today.
Dad... Mom...
Angel?
I...
...my dad... and mom.
I'll never forgive you!
I'll kill you...
I swear, I'll kill you!
Someday, I will!
I see. So Fraxinus was...
Anyway, I'm glad you're safe.
We're in Ratatoskr's underground base.
You all should come, too,
once your pickup arrives.
How do you know where we are?
Whose phone do you think you're on?
Oh...
Looks like they're there.
I'll fill you in on the rest
once you're here.
Hold up, Kotori.
The thing is, Origami...
Good work, Ellen.
Your performance was superb.
No, I took one too many direct hits.
The enemy crew had some talented individuals.
I see... Then let's hope a good number
of them survived then.
More importantly, Ike...
Yeah, I know.
Understandably, this I didn't predict.
To think she would become a Spirit...
Ah, such a pity, too.
But you're smiling, Ike.
Oops, my bad.
And? Where is she now?
It seems like her reaction suddenly vanished.
Could she have Spirit wave
suppression powers?
You think so, too?
If she's a Spirit, she knows
she'll be hunted by us.
Of course she'd hide herself.
I wonder...
That would be smart, but...
The fact we have trouble
understanding them...
...is what makes Spirits Spirits.
You never know. She might be
watching over us as we speak.
Now then, was Origami able
to achieve her goal in the end?
If I'm to be perfectly honest,
I really hope Origami makes
her wish come true.
That's not like me to say at all.
Have you been out in
the moonlight too long?
Oh, it's no big deal.
Sometimes I happen to be
in this sort of mood.
"Kaguya Yamai" "Tohka Yatogami"
"Yuzuru Yamai" "Miku Izayoi"
What the hell?!
What? What is it?
The moon! The moon's...!
"Tengu City Municipal Hospital"
Shido! What's happening out there?!
Kotori, what is this?!
A Spirit! But, I don't get it...
This powerful, without any warning?
Kotori?!
This reaction is no normal Spirit!
It's an Inverse!
Are you okay, Shido?
Yeah, thanks.
We have to save the other people!
Everyone, help me out!
Where'd that Spirit come from?
Ori... gami?
What the hell happened to you?
Origami!
Origami Tobiichi's a Spirit?
Listen, Shido... Prepare
yourself emotionally.
"Exam Room"
"Internal Medicine"
No matter who it may be,
a Spirit is a Spirit.
You'll have to capture Origami Tobiichi.
Yeah, I know.
Shido!
I don't know what happened to Origami.
But, if there's one person who can
bring her back, it's you, Shido.
Yeah, you're right.
Glad to see you understand.
If you started to whine
and complain about it,
I was ready to toss you through the sky.
Pledge. Kaguya and I will steer
you towards Master Origami.
Shido, please go and open up her eyes again.
Wait for me, Darling! I'll be
sad if you forget about me!
Look out!
Yoshino!
L-Let us take care of
everything on the ground!
With Zadkiel's power,
I think I can hold her off!
Hmph. I might as well help out, too, then.
All this debris means nothing if
I turn it into fluffy cotton puffs.
Natsumi...
Thanks, everyone!
Come on, let's go!
I'll open up the way!
Gotcha!
Acknowledged.
Whoa!
Praise. You're pretty good.
I appreciate that.
Go when I draw out her attack!
I won't last long!
Kaguya, Yuzuru! C'mon!
Leave it to me!
Acknowledged. Let's go!
I think not. We'll have no
meddling with the Inverse.
Shido!
Rescue! Raphael, El Nahash!
It's been a while, Shido Itsuka.
I could've done without seeing you again.
She's comparable to even Princess that time.
What a magnificent Inverse.
Ike will be delighted.
Screw you! We won't let you take Origami!
Barking at me like some dog
isn't going to accomplish anything.
Be silent and--
Yuzuru!
Response!
Origami!
Origami! It's me, Shido!
Can you hear me?!
All right...
Ori... gami...
Shit!
I've gotta get back to Origami!
Fraxinus?!
Looks like you went all out.
Kotori!
Pull back for now... is what I'd like to say.
But I don't think we can
afford that in this situation.
Our transport device is hanging in there,
so we'll send you over to Ori--
Kotori!
This is...
Long time no see, Shido.
Kurumi! What's your deal
at a time like this?!
Oh, my, has the great Shido completely
forgotten what my goal actually is?
At a time like this, you say?
In fact, what better time?
I can't let an opportunity
like this slip away.
Kurumi, please! Don't get in my way!
I have to save them!
I have to save Origami!
Ah, but that's hopeless.
Nobody's voice is going
to reach Origami as she is.
And by that I mean everyone, including you.
What could she have possibly
seen on her trip over there?
Well, anyway... It's time
to do what I came to do.
It's time, Zaphkiel!
Let's get this started!
Didn't I tell you already?
It's hopeless, no matter what you try.
It doesn't hurt?
What'd you do?
What indeed.
Borrowing that phrase you people say...
Now, let's begin our date!
Cicadas?
Why isn't the city destroyed?
Isn't this... Tengu City?
Ms. Tammie!
Um, how is it that you know my nickname?
C'mon, what are you talking about?
It's me, Shido Itsuka!
Wait, are you trying to hit on me?
I'm very sorry though.
I have somewhere to be.
Pardon me.
That was Ms. Tammie, right?
Kurumi!
You won't find me. I'm in a different
time than you are now, Shido.
What do you mean?
With Zaphkiel's last bullet, Yod Bet,
I sent you to Tengu City five years ago.
Five years ago?!
Take me back to where I belong!
--I don't have time for
your screwing around!
--Are you sure about that?
--I don't have time for
your screwing around!
The only way to reverse the
disaster unfolding in the present...
...is to deal with Origami over on that side.
Origami?
Yes...
So you're telling me Origami went
back five years to kill Phantom?
"Arai Shopping Arcade"
That's exactly it.
But if that's true, why would Origami
go Inverse in our original time?!
What in the world happened
to her when she came here?
That is something even I don't know.
To find out exactly that, and to reverse it,
is why I shot you with Yod Bet.
I see...
But, Kurumi... Why would you do this?
Using your Angel for someone else?
Yes, I know...
If I had to say,
it's because I want proof.
Proof that history can be changed.
Even becoming that which she hates,
her feet still trudge on.
Crossing time, defying God...
What lies at the end of her road?
"Episode Nine:
'Tengu City, Five Years Ago'"